ED]
OMDAT
I'm recording with the teacher's voice.
We're working on that.
Thank you for watching
Maybe he likes you.
It's love.
I know it's love
I don't know what I'm feeling
I cry when I'm comfortable
I cry because I love you
I don't know, we're so close
But our hearts are further apart than that
I reach out my hand to you
A warmth I can't touch
Still sleeping in my memory
Dreams are flowers blooming little by little in the wind
To be born with this voice
My dream is waiting for me in the wind with my eyes out
Alone and until my wish comes true
I nod my head as if I'm about to cry
I'm feeling better with that guy
You and I are too close
I can tell you all about our adventures
We've just started to make faces at each other
I'm starting to get kind of shy
If you like me tomorrow
I'd murmur
This hot feeling in my heart
I'd post it on social media.
I'm interested in this picture.
I'm only interested in the pictures that were taken
Baby, shake your shoulder
The lyrics are so hard to understand
It's been so long!
It's been two years since this show?
It's only the fourth time in two years!
And the audience
This is the first time
This is the first time I've been able to do it.
Today's performance
The downside of having a maxed-out
The downside is that the pillars
near the pillars
about 20 people standing in the middle.
standing in the middle.
I can't see anything about me.
I woke up today's guest
before, because he was so scared.
I tried not to sit there too much.
But today
But today, they're all in there.
I'm sorry about this.
You'll just have to concentrate on the songs.
Okay.
Let's move on to the show.
We've got 35 minutes.
I haven't had a chance to put on my makeup. I haven't had a chance to change my clothes.
I haven't even eaten my udon yet.
I'd like to eat udon if I can. I'll do my best.
I'll start eating udon 15 minutes ago.
Oh, my God! How's it going?
Bon appétit!
It's too good! Oh, man!
It's so good!
Breathe!
From here?
Mmm!
Shaved ice with cheese.
I don't think I've ever had shaved ice with cheese.
No.
Just your face, your face and your voice.
You're so good with the food.
Yeah.
He's too good at good food.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Too good at the good parts.
After the show, please.
Okay, well, good luck. It's been ten minutes.
Let's get it done.
I'll do my best.
I managed to get it done in time.
Okay, I'll put in the compact.
I can't remember anything about any of the MCs.
Oh, no.
I didn't think about it, but you don't remember.
Sorry.
It's coming in this one.
Yes, I have to do it.
Oh, you want to open it?
Oh, my God.
It's not ready yet.
Are you sure this is a good idea?
Yes, sir.
Here we go.
Yes, please.
Yes, sir.Yes, sir.
[Applause]
Thank you very much for coming today to the 16th anniversary of AKB48 Yuki Kashiwagi's solo performance debut.
Before the performance begins, I would like to make a few requests to our guests.
Today, April 8, is the 16th anniversary of Yuki Kashiwagi's debut, so I will be giving a solo performance.
Are you ready to get excited?
The show will start soon. Please wait a little longer.
This is Yuki Kashiwagi, aka Yukirii.
I'll be right here.
Hey, uh...
Official, online site, online store official.
What?
Online store. I'm screwed. I don't think I can do this.
I'm off.
Welcome.
Pink on stage, just after dusk.
It's brighter than that day.
You're looking at me right now, my heart.
Maybe Maybe
I don't have that kind of courage.
Something more certain
Maybe Maybe
I don't have the courage
I'll stay like this, stretching out my shoulders
Happiness Maybe
This is Yuki Kashiwagi, aka Yukirin with Aiken Beauty Salon.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to be able to do a solo performance.
It's the first time for me to perform my voice,
It's the best.
Oh, you are further away from me than that.
I can't wait to see you, but it's not going to change.
Sad dreams always turn to tears again
Chigure and memories are always too beautiful
Until I can finally sleep
I'll deflect it all away
Come on, it's getting cold
Before the dreams turn to night
Let that sadness of today fade away
A little bit of love is good
Maybe something good will happen tomorrow
If I'm a little stronger
I'd be there for you
I can see you happy too
Thank you for your time.
You okay?
Yeah, I think so.
All right.
Let's go.
I'm fired up.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
I'll see you again, I promise.
You'll see me again.
I promise you'll never forget me.
I don't want to be the star of our dreams
You're so sadly out of reach
Like we're in love
That's why I can't see you anymore
I don't want you near me no matter what
Thank you very much for your time.
I'm more tired than I thought I'd be.
Look at this.
It's my QUO card.
I'll show you mine alone.
I got a bunch of old ones from the office.
But I'm still too embarrassed to use them.
I've finally settled down.
I knew it would be hard to have a break from the show.
I sometimes throw up, or I have to take a break during the unit performance.
And there are parts that I don't sing.
If you sing by yourself all the time and talk all the way to the MC...
It's a lot of power, but it was a lot of fun.
If you see someone crying, it's probably a girl.
There will be a second performance in an hour and a half.
The second show is in an hour and a half.
Let's have the udon from earlier.
Ta-da!
What's that? You ate a lot.
I'm going to eat now. Thank you for your hard work.
The second show is about to start.
The whole time...
I've been thinking about MCing.
I want to make a cute video.
I want to make a video.
I'm making a video here.
I'm making a video.
It's so cute!
Here you go.
Oh, wow.
Bon appétit!
Today, April 8th, is the 16th anniversary of my debut as a 3rd term student, Yuko Hashigami.
I will be able to do a solo performance today!
Congratulations!
No way.
It's our 16th anniversary.
It's going to be 17 years.
It's just about...
That's not just a "just".
Half of my life.I've spent half of my life
I've spent half my life as an AKB.
Thank you.
Too beautiful. Axiom set.
Every man should say it.
More mouths to feed. On our side.
So heavy
All loved her for her treasure.
They'll be asking you to come home
I've got something to show you
Too beautiful, too beautiful, Axia set
Hallelujah, hallelujah, hallelujah
Hallu, hallu, hallu, hallu
You love me
I'll make the sunrise
Love, love, love, gather up the love
Ah, the fireworks of love have scattered
The spring that bloomed so beautifully
Why did it get loose and go somewhere?
I think of you, weakling, I love you
Stay by the side of the sky
You're still in that town
Yesterday, I told you how sad I am now
Look, smile
I wanna go
Love Trick, Beyond the Time
Love Trick, let's go home
Keep it close to your chest
Come on, let's travel
I wanna go
Love Trick
Where are you?
Long Distance
I've been looking all over for you
I have a heart
A dream is a dream
Will be lost in the shadows
But I remember the first sadness
I remember
When I met you
Under the summer sky
Running through my heart
Running through the song
That's what I thought
Throwing everything I've got
Oh, the dream
In the wind
A flower blooming little by little
Hold on to this thought
Fly with me
My dream is
In the wind
I hold out my hand
Stoneback is standing
Someday, I'm sure
High in the sky
What?
Let him speak locally!
You're Mr. S on YouTube!
Ha-ha-ha!
What are you doing?
I put it on YouTube today.
What?
It's Mr. S!
Wait a minute!
No, wait a minute!
No, that's too much!
You're more excited than I am!
I'm so happy!
First anniversary?
Talking?
Happy 16th anniversary!
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
Yes, thank you!
Thank you very much, YouTube.
Okay, I'm going to take you on a loop.
If you don't want to be on YouTube, you can hide your face, okay?
Okay.
This is our 16th anniversary fans!
Yeah!
Congratulations!
So, today, April 8, is the 16th anniversary of VICTORIA's debut! What a surprise! Look at all of you!
Look at this! Why? Are you really graduating?
It's so big, but thank God! Such a cute guy!
Even though I do concerts in many different places and do many different activities, I still enjoy the theater and I love it, so I want to keep performing at the theater.
I love the theater, so I want to continue to value theater performances as I always have.
I hope you will come to the theater! I will do my best in my 17th year wearing this costume with an innocent look on my face!
I'll be waiting for you at the theater! So, everyone, please look forward to our 17th year!
That's all for now, Yuki-Ringo and President Yuki! See you soon!
Thank you for watching!